https://pianet.com/f/privacy

PIA Branding ProgramLeadershipCalendarLinksContact Us
About UsAbout PIAPresident's MessageLocal PIA AssociationsBoard of DirectorsPIA Insurance FoundationSponsorship OpportunitiesMeetingsJoinAgentsCompaniesMember BenefitsOverviewInsurance Products for You and Your AgencyE & O InsuranceCyber Liability InsurancePenn National Insurance Agents' Umbrella ProgramInsurance Products from the PIA TrustInsurance Products to SellPIA Market AccessFlood Insurance through The HartfordPIA Cyber InsuranceAgency Revenue ToolsMarketing Materials for PIA MembersPIA Branding Program — marketing materials for PIA membersAgency Marketing Guide — marketing tips for PIA membersPIA DMV: PIA's Direct Marketing VaultFloodbroker.com — making flood sales easier for PIA membersFlood Insurance Marketing Support CenterServices & Resources for PIA MembersIdealTraits, Insurance Agency Hiring Made EasyAVYST eForms Wizard —
Automated Workflow ManagementAgency Agreement Review ServiceDocIT for Agents — a Traffic Violation Reporting ToolInsurance Business Practices & Technical InformationPIA Member DiscountsACORD End User License for PIA MembersAgency Web Sites from PIA and Broadridge Advisor Solutions (formerly Emerald)Alamo Rent a Car Central Licensing BureauCVS Prescription Discount Card for PIA Members, Their Employees and ClientsFree & Discounted SubscriptionsOMNIA Employee ProfilingRough Notes Advantage-Plus Solution United Parcel Service (UPS)The PIA Logo for Member UseEducationPublicationsPIA Connection MagazinePIA Connection ArchivePIA Connection AdvertisersAgency Marketing GuideAgent to AgentGuide to Using RSS FeedsAdvertise with PIA NationalWhitelisting Emails From PIA NationalPIA Logo WearThe PIA PartnershipPartnership OverviewClosing the Gap – Growth & ProfitAgency Touch PointsReaching Gen YPractical Guide to Successful PlanningPerpetuation CentralE & ONews CenterInsurance NewsPIA Press ReleasesNews About PIAAll HeadlinesMedia InquiriesGovernment AffairsPIA Advocacy BlogPolicy and Advocacy Priorities Current IssuesAgent Licensing UniformityCrop InsuranceCybersecurityFlood InsuranceHealthcare ReformSmall Business & Tax ReformState RegulationTerrorism InsuranceGrassroots Action AlertsPIA Advocacy DayPIAPACArchived IssuesCertificates of InsuranceNatural DisasterTort ReformThe PIA PartnershipPartnership OverviewReady For Everything: Crisis Resource Hub for Insurance AgentsWinning@TalentAgency Journey MappingCyber 101Small Business Insurance & The InternetClosing the Gap – Growth & ProfitAgency Touch PointsReaching Gen YPractical Guide to Successful PlanningThe PIA Partnership News
You
are here:Home
›
Privacy PolicyInfoPrivacy PolicyLast changed April 30, 2012The National Association of Professional Insurance Agents ("PIA") respects the privacy of its members and other visitors to its Web Site ("PIANET"). PIA has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to user privacy. The following applies to the information gathering and dissemination practices for information collected on or submitted to PIANET. Please also see the Terms of Use which all users of PIANET agree to abide by as a condition of using PIANET.How Information Is CollectedInformation You Provide: PIANET collects personally identifiable information from you if you choose to provide this information to us. In a few areas on PIANET, we ask you to provide information — or log-in as a PIA member, a PIA or PIA chartered affiliate employee, a customer, or a PIA partner (collectively known as "Authenticated Users") — to enable PIA: to verify whether you are entitled to access and use certain information, materials and services available from PIANET; to enhance your site visit; to assist you with customer service or technical support issues; to follow up with you after your visit; to provide information about products and services; or to otherwise support your customer and/or member relationship with PIA. While failure to provide this information may mean that you cannot access and use certain information, materials and services on PIANET or PIA partner web sites, providing personally identifiable information on PIANET and logging-in as an Authenticated User are completely optional.Information That Is Automatically Collected: Basic contact information (name, company name, address, phone number, email address, member identification number, etc.) about Authenticated Users is uploaded from PIA's membership database to PIANET to enable Authenticated Users to log-in and access password-protected information and programs.PIANET does automatically collect information that does not identify users personally. Via Web server logs, for example, PIA may monitor statistics such as the number of people that visit PIANET, which page(s) are visited on PIANET, from which domain our visitors come (e.g., aol.com, yahoo.com, etc.), and which browsers people use to visit PIANET (e.g., Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome, Microsoft Internet Explorer, Safari etc.).Cookies: A "cookie" is a small file that is placed on your hard drive by a Web page server. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can be read only by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.Each time you initiate a session on PIANET the site sets the cookie in order to identify you and determine your access privileges. Cookies do not store any of the personal information that you have provided to the site. They are simply identifiers. Clicking on this box will store the cookie on your hard drive so that you will not have to log in each time you visit PIANET.You have the ability to delete cookie files from your hard drive at any time. However, you should know that cookies may be necessary to provide you with access to much of the content and features of PIANET. We use cookie technology to enable Authenticated Users to move quickly and securely through access-controlled areas of PIANET and to take advantage of certain useful features on PIANET.How Information Is UsedInformation you provide and information that is uploaded to PIANET from PIA's membership database may be used to verify whether you are entitled to access and use certain information, materials and services available from PIANET; to enhance your site visit; to assist you with customer service or technical support issues; to follow up with you after your visit; to provide information about products and services; or to otherwise support your customer and/or member relationship with PIA.PIA strives to keep the personal information you provide to us when using PIANET and information that is uploaded to PIANET from PIA's membership database confidential. Agents or contractors of PIA who are given access to your personal information are required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for PIA.We may disclose information you provide to us and information that is uploaded to PIANET from PIA's membership database to third parties in order to complete a transaction that you requested or to improve your customer experience. We may also outsource some tasks, including the operation of certain Web Site functions, that require access to information you supply online. On occasion, PIA may also provide data supplied online to third parties that offer products and services. We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to comply with the law or legal process.PIA monitors PIANET "traffic" statistics using information that does not identify users personally so we may improve PIANET. We use an outsourcing program to assist us in analyzing this data. Aggregated statistics may also be provided to advertisers and other third parties, but the statistics contain no personal information.SecurityPIA takes steps to protect against the loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration of personally identifiable information. We utilize industry standard SSL encryption when accepting credit card information during our online checkout process. Access to some computer data and files at PIA are secured by password coding with access to personally identifiable information strictly limited to those employees who need access in order to carry out their job responsibilities. Our network is behind a firewall designed to prevent unauthorized access.How You Can Access or Correct Your DataAuthenticated Users may access and correct personal information in their PIANET profile. To the extent that other personally identifiable information has been received by PIA and is currently stored, please contact the appropriate department of PIA to review and/or change this information.Means of RedressIf any PIANET user suspects PIA has handled its personal information in a manner that does not comply with this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email to web@pianet.org or by calling (703) 836-9340.Other Web SitesPIANET contains "links" to other, external Internet Web Sites who may have privacy policies and procedures that differ from those of PIA.Privacy Policy ChangesPIA reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Updated versions of the Privacy Policy will appear on PIANET and are effective immediately. You are responsible for regularly reviewing the Privacy Policy. Continued use of PIANET after any such changes constitutes your consent to such changes.
National Association of Professional Insurance AgentsPrivacyTerms of UseSite MapCopyright © 2000-2019
